Contact

heet.vbt14@spt.pdpu.ac.in

www.linkedin.com/in/heet-voraba8a45123 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Oil & Gas
Outside Sales
Field Service

Heet Vora

Brand Consultant

Gujarat

Summary

Experienced Franchise Business Consultant with a demonstrated history of working in the marketing and advertising industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Offshoring, Business-to-Business (B2B), Technical Product Sales, and Microsoft Excel. Strong sales professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Petroleum Engineering from Pandit Deendayal Energy University.

Experience

AMBE Advisors
Founder and CEO
January 2022 - Present (6 months)
India

I am founder Of AMBE Advisors. AMBE (Above Marketing Beyond Everything) Advisors are experts and pandits of Digital Marketing Space. Having Total 3 Years of experience in Social Media Marketing, We will help you from You Logo Creation to Lead generation for your Enterprise.

WOODDY JHONE'S PIZZA

6 months

Business Development Consultant August 2021 - January 2022 (6 months) India

- 1). First point of contact for Franchise in Western Region Of India;
- 2). Improved business operations in all areas of entrepreneurship, such as operational, financial and commercial;
- 3). Provided training to franchisees, supervisors and managers in the following areas:
- Various operational training courses (on-the-job)
- Effective supervision (classic)

- Prepare reports on the business operations of the franchises, issue advice and draw up improvement plans;
- 4). Facilitated the opening and onboarding of all new locations from start to finish;
- 5). Oversee franchisees and advise them on marketing strategies to grow their business.
- 6). Developed efficient system for daily cash flow from inception of franchise store. Managed payment schedule for vendors and payroll. Managed acquisitions, prepared invoices and updated accounting records.

Digital Marketing Consultant August 2021 - January 2022 (6 months) India

Managed online communications via digital channels to increase brand reputation and ads for multiple Wooddy Jhone's Outlets.

- 1). Monitored conversations and proactively reached out to key influencers and bloggers within community to build;
- 2). Drafted reports and presentations for senior management to track incoming customer reviews, social media analytics, and accomplishments that could be easily understood from a sales perspective;
- 3). Developed partnerships with local businesses and organizations to promote events;
- 4). Designed new, engaging content and Developed communications and customer engagement strategies, including offers and discounts, to enhance brand-awareness;
- 5). Developed new industry relationships via E-mail and social media including management and editing content to develop engaging content;
- 6). Supported new business development, contributed to proposals and participated in social media strategy/campaign pitches.

Blue Heritage Ltd

Resourcing Specialist December 2020 - July 2021 (8 months)

Milton Keynes, England, United Kingdom

- 1). Responsible for providing the highest level of 180" recruitment at all levels.
- 2). Deliver high quality professional candidates, guiding them through the selection process.
- 3). Drive excellent business relationships with candidates and Talent acquisition team ensuring compliance and best practice across the function
- 4). Attract, identify and recruit both Permanent and contract roles across a number of sectors and locations.
- 5). Develop an effective resourcing plan to facilitate a proactive approach to resourcing and candidate pipeline.
- 6). Leverage online recruiting resources like CVLibrary, Linkedin and many more and in-house systems to identify and recruit the very best candidates.
- 7). Conduct CV mining on various job boards and professional networking sites to pro-actively source candidate for all levels of roles.
- 8). Work with Talent acquisition and gain a direct understanding of the pressures / requirements of the project.
- 9). Maintain accurate documentation on all candidates to ensure a robust and thorough audit trail ensuring 100% compliant.

Blue Heritage is a leading recruitment consultancy across the UK & Europe that specialises in the Energy, Technology, Blockchain and EV sectors and we aim to provide a premium experience for the recruitment needs for all clients and candidates. We have vast experience across the whole spectrum of Energy including renewables and energy storage, as well as technology and IT Analytics, Electric Vehicle and Blockchain & Cryptocurrency roles. We cover Contract, Permanent and Fixed Term vacancies for clients throughout Europe so if you're looking for your next role or to recruit a key individual for your team, please get in touch.

Dangee Dums - India
Executive - Business Development
September 2019 - August 2020 (1 year)
Gujarat, India

- 1. Sourcing & Closing the deals with Hight End Properties as per the SIS(Store in Store) strategy for outlets across the region.
- 2. Conduct market analysis and feasibility study for store expansions at Properties across the West region.
- 3. Negotiation & closure of transactions followed by documentation of term sheet & agreement closure
- 4. P&L formulations & ROI analysis in coordination with Account, Legal and marketing department .
- 5. Ensure complete coordination with project & operation team for timely launch of the store.
- 6. Successfully opened 1 Company store in Western Region.

Dangee Dums began its sweet journey in 2010 as a boutique store of high-end chocolates and caught the public's eye with its 'Cake of the Week' campaign. Since then, we pivoted to bringing forward one of the finest signature cakes, cupcakes, chocolates, ice creams, cookies and savories. We transitioned over a period of time into a master brand with sub-brands based on the cakery format with 38 stores across 4 cities.

Adani Gas Field Sales Officer March 2019 - September 2019 (7 months) Ahmedabad

Established customer relationships across all levels of management mainly in B2B Sector. Built brand awareness and created brand preference among sales reps at all major companies. Conducted product feature and benefit trainings to increase sell through. Planned and maintained a territorial coverage plan for all targeted companies in Ahmedabad. Worked closely with professionals to identify challenges, understand needs, analyze available tools, and provide appropriate solutions integrating Abbott products for improved patient outcomes, in a cost-effective manner.

Education

Pandit Deendayal Energy University

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Petroleum Engineering · (June 2015 - June 2019)